Software in Business
For the following questions, open a new notepad or word document and write your answers in it. Call it "software-in-business.txt" and make sure you save after you finish.
Choose a previous job role or educational setting to consider. Make a list of the technological systems you interacted with directly over the course of that role.

Transportation Electrification Analyst
JIRA
Teams
Microsoft 365
Sharepoint
Smartsheet
VirtualPeaker Platforms

Consider the wider needs of the business or school you were a part of. Make a list of the other types of systems that were used (or, if you're not sure exactly, probably used) in other parts of the organization.
Sightling to track data
Databases for EV users

For each of the items in the first and second list, write a brief description of what value they brought to the organization.
Project management
Client engagement
Tracking tasks between team
Tracking progresss
Real time Data collection management
